Thank you for watching!
Delicious.
What was the first job we ever had?
What was it?
Wasn't it the Ebitu Globalization Project? That's right.
That's right. After that was the Ebitu Achievement.
That was 10 years ago. The time of Ebbival.
Fourteen years.
The great thing about Ebitu is, when I went to the live show, I thought
There were so many more girl kids.
That's right. They were of a younger generation, and some were in junior high school or high school.
In my opinion, idol concerts are mostly for guys.
Now it is 40%? Forty percent?
That's about half. Nearly half are girls.
That's amazing. That's right.
What made you decide to do that?
I wonder. Since then?
Is it like that since you started doing shows with us back then? No, it started gradually, gradually, gradually increasing from then on.
And now it's over. So what's going on? I wonder.
You don't understand, do you? We knew what was going on. So, did you have any kind of plan with the principal to increase the number of female fans?
Wasn't there some kind of strategy or something like that?
The principal finally mentioned something like that. Yes, since last year. That's a little late. Our audience is growing, already.
By the time the principal realized it, it was already growing. It's like he's trying to make it cooler.
But that's not his credit at all. Not at all. It's already growing. It's increasing. Not at all.
It's not that it's increasing on its own, or maybe it's just the times we live in. I wonder. But when I talk to girls at handshake events, I get the impression that there are many girls who feel very close to me, not as friends, but as motivation to work hard because girls of their generation are working hard.
I have the impression that many of them feel very close to me.
I'm working hard at this, but Ai-chan is working hard like this, so I'm going to work hard, too!
I wonder if they feel that kind of friendliness and live on with us because there are many girls like that.
Is that so? And Maya too? I am the same way.
No, Mayamo seems to have a lot of guys who are serious fans.
I think there are a lot of guys who are serious fans of Maya. Like Mr. Takeda. People like that.
They have weird hair like that. There might be a lot of unique people.
Each one has his/her own personality. However, I am one of those who have many girls.
There are quite a lot of girls. I am,
I have a lot of men from my father's generation and women around the same age as me, from around 15 years old to women in their 20s, 30s, and 40s,
You know the individual handshake lanes? In those lanes, there are men who shake hands with more than half of the girls.
What is that? Do they say, "I like 2D too"?
There are those who do,
And then there are those who just want to talk about their daily lives and whatnot.
I'd like to make small talk. I'm not sure what I've gotten myself into.
I'd like to... well, I guess I'm closer to you now than I was a while ago.
There were so many kids who became fans after seeing DVDs of Tastas, or DVDs of the shows I did with shooting stars, or clippings of various famous scenes,
Even though everyone in that show was a piece of shit.
Are you aware of that?
Yes, I am.
I see.
Yes, I am aware of it.
I do too.
All of us. All of us. All the staff, too. When all the different fishing ponds and traps came out all at once.
I thought it was stupid. I thought, "Let them come out in order, all at once. Then, all at once, they rattled in here, and some strange characters came in.
I was like, "Wait a minute, let's do separate shots. Three incidents happened at once. It was tough. I couldn't do it anymore.
I love it when people are genuinely enjoying themselves, in a real atmosphere, and it's really interesting.
I really want to do it. I really want to do it.
There are so many fans of Ebinaka, I'm so glad to hear that!
I'm glad to hear that.
I thought you'd be okay with it... but I'm not here for the shrimp show today.
You should come to that one!
It's not a family anymore!
Well, I'm here!
I'm here wearing an Ebichu T-shirt!
Which way!
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
It's a little frustrating.
I had a fascinating feeling.
Maybe there are a lot of Ebi Junior fans like that.
I'm sure there are a lot of them.
I've grown to love the artists we play with.
I stopped coming to the shows.
It's a synergistic effect.
It happens the other way around, too.
That's true, and I'm grateful for that.
I'm grateful for that, too.
I'll be able to make more friends like that.
And so are the customers.
How many times do you want to do it?
I want to do it.
I've got 10 members now.
I heard that there are 5 who have not been involved with Mr. Nagaehoshi.
Yeah, those kids pack a punch.
I want you to experience it.
You say that like it's an attraction.
New attraction.
But it's new. We got five new members.
Half of them at once.
What do you think? How do you feel about the relationship, even in Nakano?
Well, I don't know.
Yes, but every day...
I do feel a generation gap. She's a sophomore in high school
That doesn't fit, because if it were Mayama, we'd be the generation that interferes, that's right, we interfere, so we don't, today's kids, great, don't interfere, great
We don't talk to each other.
So, even though there's a generation gap, we're all on the same page when it comes to makeup and fashion, which is what girls like.
Everyone is dark and mature.
You know, Yasumoto, he was so funny, he wanted to wear a super tie.
Like a pin-up comedian
I still want to be like that with Yasumoto, if I were in a store.
Um...
Did she say, "Takei-san's shoes are fashionable"?
I said.
I don't want to be told by you.
You're absolutely tacky!
I've become stylish.
That's what I'm really thinking.
I'm thinking it.
I'm glad.
No, I said, "These shoes are no good.
I sold them right away.
Sold them? Oh, my God.
You sold them? Back then. Back then.
But now you've simplified it. It's more grown-up.
I mean, you were Pink Purser, right? You had a good image of Pink Purser.
She's grown up. She's calmed down.
The shocking pink image of the Pink Purser.
I used to dress like a rock star.
Takegami-san's fashion was very similar to my father's.
Like Pink Purser, he wears a terrorem adha shirt.
And he also wore an adha shirt of love.
He loved my dad so much, my dad used to get his hands on him in front of the house.
Hey, that's disrespectful.
What do you mean "just like that"?
Who cares about tentacle fashion?
I think that kind of thing is bad for the world.
I think it's bad for the world if you eat in the dining room...
Please don't tell me where you live.
We were working on a show together back then and we had a tendency to be like...
We often talked about that.
I don't know... it's faint, but...
So you can guess the obvious one, can't you?
Well, you know...
Kashihagi is the middle...
No. 5
It's a female gundam... but she's banned from the office for overdoing it.
I'm going to make a funny face, which is not the kind of face this idol would make... and then next time I'll make a funny face like this.
I was really upset at how it could be done so automatically, and I really love Mr. Chain, so yeah, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right.
Wow... but the two shooting stars... because that guy...
I know he's in our fan club... and yes... there's a few on display... and he says that's one more...
The whole family is rooting for you... but...
But...
Kobayashi and Yasumoto are for me, me, me.
You're not getting away with it.
I want a good Ballenger.
No, but Yasumoto was a ping-pong player
Thank you very much.
But, I mean, now that you mention it...
Please.
If I tell you first, you'll know.
Well, there are a lot of Chuo-san fans.
Wait a minute.
But you do have your father's looks.
I'm attracted to him.
And you're so sweet, Mr. Takei.
I was so happy when he talked about boobs.
Did I just say boobs?
You just said that, didn't you?
You're the one who's totally talking about boobs.
Yes, I am.
You can't even be bothered to do that.
I'm a bad idol.
You're right, I shouldn't say that.
A lot, a lot, a lot, a lot.
I didn't get a lot of tongue in cheek.
Plenty, pie.
You talked a lot.
You ever been to one of those towns?
You don't usually go there?
I don't usually go there.
There's usually too much 5:00.
It's dangerous.
I'll tell you what.
I can't miss it.
You're right.
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
That was close.
I'm so glad...
You talked a lot, which made me happy.
I remember how happy I was to hear a girl talk so much.
We've managed to communicate like this.
I don't understand
What about Mayama?
Yeah...
So...
Tadahide-san...
Is that right?
That's right.
There are many Tadahide-san in this house.
First of all, there are many Tadahide-san.
Many of them are Tadahide-san.
But Mr. Takigami talks a lot.
What's with that? You're not trying to find the good in a family style.
When you first came out with the shooting star, you were probably referring to Tadahide's gags.
That's right. Well, I mean, not me.
Ebichu remembered my name, but he messed around with Tackey...
But the staff couldn't remember my name at all.
Oh, really? It's not Ebichu's show, but other shows... and they say, "Chuei-san and the others...
It's hard for Chueisans. They get a touch of it.
I saw a show where they kept calling me Mr. Onoe, and finally they said, "This is no relation to Takigami.
So you remembered my name, and you treated me like a human being.
I'd like to find the Takigami group... first Yasumoto, then.
And the rest?
The rest are Nakayama, Hirota, Aiai...
What about Kobayashi?
I don't think I can pick Kobayashi.
Hoshino is Nakagami.
I think so.
I don't know. Basically, it's neither.
I'm not really interested.
I know that. And Nakayama's not either.
I want to sleep. I want to sleep.
I'd rather eat cucumbers.
And Matsuno? Which was Matsuno, Rina?
I think she liked Takee.
Everyone liked Takee-san.
Really?
I really like her.
It's just which side you're on, it's different.
I'd say they're different.
Matsuno was crazy about Umiki.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
When he first came out and saw Kaiki looking so nervous
He was laughing so hard.
In a way that I like.
I thought maybe he likes people who are a little weird like that.
But he was laughing so hard at me.
I thought maybe he was more interested in me than the people around him.
I thought it was me.
That's what I thought. I think he mentioned my name more often at the end of the recording.
I think I would say, "You know, I was talking to Mr. Takigami at that time.
But still, it's the same for everyone.
Today's Takigami.
Because of the way he talked.
That's it, that's it.
He's really messing around with it.
The highlight of the day was, after all, Takigami-san.
Please leave us a story.
Please leave me with one story.
It was like a reward day for me.
It's true!
And we were in a sensitive period, so I'm sure there were times when we cried a lot and they had to stop recording.
You cried a lot.
We cried about that, too.
It was a surprise.
Like I was going to snap.
Like I'd suddenly snap at something I didn't understand.
I'm Hanana Takigami. It's funny.
It's traumatizing, isn't it?
That's right. We did it again.
I miss it.
One thing I regret... is that I was the one who set up the surprise.
That's right.
We did that a couple of times, right? I was the instigator for all of them.
I've never been set up.
Really?
I guess that's just how it is with the oldest.
Whenever something like that happens, it's usually Mayasa.
You're the only one who should know about it.
There are a lot of instigators.
If there was an opportunity to work with Ms. Nagareyama again...
If you ever have a chance to do something like that with Mr. Nagareyama...
If you do...
You said that.
I got beat up.
It's disgusting... but...
It's getting worse.
Eventually, you'll say, "Well, that's good.
But then...
Really?
You don't add new comedians, do you?
Additional members?
Well, it's not often that a shooting star is added from here on out.
So, I was worried. For a while, you were worried about that shooting star,
Oh, yes, yes, I've heard of that.
I was wondering if it was a crucian carp or not.
You must be worried, right? They were such good friends.
We had a big fight on Godotan.
We had a big fight.
But, yes, we did fight, but we've known each other since high school, so we were doing shots like that fight. Behind the scenes.
It just happened to be on that TV, on Godotan.
I just showed it to him.
I wonder what it was.
And then, when I go on other shows,
I mean, for goodness' sake, they'd give me a ship or a character.
Then, Nakamoe would open the switch and start a fight with me.
Then I would get in on it and say, "Wow!
Then we would get into a real fight.
And then we would really fight again that day.
Hee!
There was a time when we had a fight.
That's right.
I had a fight too.
After a while, it stopped and things became normal, but lately it's like we're all shipwrecked.
Oh, I see.
So, when I went to Ebichu's concert and went to the backstage, Kobayashi immediately said, "Well, well, be friendly with me!
Well, well, be friendly with me! I understand.
I understand.
I thought, "That's what I'm talking about.
I'm fine now.
Hmmm.
Yes, please rest assured.
That's good. Is that when you decided to bring in a new member?
We decided to make a trio. In private, Mr. Tamura is like a new member.
Like a center microphone. Our manager is in the middle and keeps the balance.
From the point of view of the youngest, he really supported Eritchu all the time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So you're probably going to be someone who watched TV or something, right?
I would definitely think it would be a junior.
I wouldn't like it if it was a junior.
I'd hate it too.
No, definitely not.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Why not?
This group has such a rich history!
We really have.
We're taking into account all the different generations.
It's amazing.
But I'm happy for you that it's been so long.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy to see you.
I'm glad to see you.
On July 17th and 18th at the Theater Hibiki in Yamanaka-ko Koryu Plaza.
We're going to hold the Binchu Summer Family Movie, or "Famie" for short, at the Lake Yamanaka Koryu Plaza Theater Hibiki on July 17th and 18th.
It's a big summer concert, so I'd be happy if you all could come and enjoy it!
Takeda-san, are you watching?
We're waiting for you! Let's be a range of mission together!
And we will hold a live concert at Saitama Super Arena on March 20!
This is the stage that Ebitu has always dreamed of standing on with the 10 of us again, so we are really looking forward to this day!
We hope that many people will be able to come and join us.
We are ex-Ebichu family who love shooting stars!
Please come to the show for sure!
We'll be waiting for you!
Manager Sano, are you watching?
Are you watching?
I'm waiting for you.
Please come to the first meeting.
Is this the first Takiyu room?
The other guest is...
Ebichu's, as expected.
Yasumoto and Mayama.
Thank you very much.
What? What? What?